# George Koutanis

I am a full stack developer experienced in Javascript and React. I am originally from Greece and now live in Southampton, UK. While growing up my engagement with computers led me to appreciate the range of possibilities with technology and sparked my passion for programming.

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

### General

JavaScript

#### Backend

NodeJS ExpressJS REST MongoDB PostgreSQL

### Frontend

React HTML CSS

### Tools and technologies

Visual Studio Code
Mocha/Jest
Git+GitHub
Docker
AWS
TDD
Agile work methods

### Links

LinkedIn
GitHub
Portfolio

### Languages

Greek - Native English - Proficient

## **EDUCATION & TRAINING**

## Full Stack Javascript - School of Applied Technology </salt>

January 2023 - April 2023 Intensive three month training program with a focus on TDD, mob programming, and applied learning.

### IEK AGIOU DIMITRIOU

September 2017 - June 2019 Associate's degree Web Development-Design

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Coopervision UK**

September 2022 - december 2022

## **Royal Mail Southampton**

December 2019 - August 2022 Mail center worker

## Athens international airport Post office

March 2019 - September 2019 Mail center worker

### **Greek Customs office**

September 2018 - February 2019 Customs agent assistant. Responsible for managing paperwork and assisting in IT related problems.

### **Hellas Electronics**

August 2014 - December 2015
Office assistant responsible for handling emails - sales on ebay, editing images and listing products on ebay.